[
  {
    "name": "Cliffords Tower",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 372079",
    "question": "There are two coats-of-arms on the 'tall' building, what animal is holding the bottom one up?",
    "answer": "cd11a8da14ceaf589eb3895adcd1d630"
  },
  {
    "name": "Crossroads",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 366050",
    "question": "As you come to a four-way crossroad, what does the shop adjacent to the church sell?",
    "answer": "deddb1176254217735982ecdb96a700e"
  },
  {
    "name": "War Memorial",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 359028",
    "question": "There is a section of old ruined wall, now serving a new purpose. What is that purpose?",
    "answer": "bd9ae213593d858b265939efa1b2c8b9"
  },
  {
    "name": "Art Gallery",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 347030",
    "question": "In the square, there is a fountain, with a figure beside it. What was his elected position?",
    "answer": "b79c374155f2d55ecc50ab2df2d96cbc"
  },
  {
    "name": "Cat Shop",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 357055",
    "question": "There is a shop specialising in furry creatures. What does the shop on its right sell?",
    "answer": "42b46a5096efdbe9b7554dee60d8d7a1"
  },
  {
    "name": "Walls over Station",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 322072",
    "question": "Get up high for this one. With busses on your right, walk forwards. What do you walk into?",
    "answer": "afb15e217840ad83a4b2b19b34452240"
  },
  {
    "name": "Victoria Bar",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 343092",
    "question": "You'll come to a 'bridge' over the road. What is its name?",
    "answer": "58ae474d026eef0c43b18cbb6d57f025"
  },
  {
    "name": "Hooting Owl Dist.",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 341059",
    "question": "Here you can see an alcohol distillery. What animal is it named after?",
    "answer": "ec69454e9bdc9de3c580ae59b183f589"
  },
  {
    "name": "Merchant Hall",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 376062",
    "question": "Find a large red door with a mighty emblem above it. What colour are the lions on the coat-of-arms?",
    "answer": "87c6c237f6e3ad9eb4669e706dfc05f8"
  },
  {
    "name": "NCEM",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 399073",
    "question": "On this street there is a national institution for something. What is that something?",
    "answer": "5ce9a33626f3329d50af8adbb439d44a"
  },
  {
    "name": "St. Andrew's",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 376044",
    "question": "You can walk all around this church. But who is it named after?",
    "answer": "060818347a4ae8edc3c365d27cf9c5f0"
  },
  {
    "name": "Stonegate Teddies",
    "location": "Grid Reference: 355045",
    "question": "You are on a famous road in York, and nearby there is a shop named after the road. What does it sell?",
    "answer": "ec4822f2d137c22e32fac858ba699e16"
  }
]
